<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stanley Blog</title>
    <link>https://zhangqi336.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Stanley Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zhangqi336.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Saying goodbye to Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://zhangqi336.github.io/reads/2019-05-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangqi336.github.io/reads/2019-05-13/</guid>
      <description>Saying goodbye to Microsoft - What I gained, lost &amp;amp; learned while working for Microsoft. (medium.com)
 It wasn’t a ‘golden cage’ I was in, it was a bubble of illusions that popped once I signed my dismissal papers. Illusions of importance, mission, friendships and luxury.
I’m 28, have learned to put myself first and spent plenty of time on self care, enough to be able to share this publicly and hopefully not to make the same mistakes in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Google&#43; Failed</title>
      <link>https://zhangqi336.github.io/reads/2019-04-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangqi336.github.io/reads/2019-04-05/</guid>
      <description>Why Google+ Failed (onezero.medium.com)
 Google Plus didn’t fail because Facebook is invulnerable.
It failed because of deep flaws embedded in it from the very start.
 It&amp;rsquo;s no news that Google is shutting down its products or services. The author worked in Google+ team and has seen how Google+ end up being one of those. He not only told us the issues and problems that caused the failure, but also what prevented it from being fixed or corrected along the way from product perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop Learning Frameworks</title>
      <link>https://zhangqi336.github.io/reads/2019-03-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangqi336.github.io/reads/2019-03-15/</guid>
      <description>Stop Learning Frameworks (sizovs.net)
 The longer a technology is on the market, the safer investment it is.
Don’t rush to learn new technology – it has a high probability of dying.
Time will show which technology is worth investing in. Time is your best advisor. Learn to wait.
Remember – frameworks, libraries and tools come and go. Time is precious.
 I loves to learn new technologies, which often turned out to be just learning new frameworks/tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microservice Architecture at Medium</title>
      <link>https://zhangqi336.github.io/reads/2019-03-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangqi336.github.io/reads/2019-03-09/</guid>
      <description>Microservice Architecture at Medium (medium.engineering)
 At Medium, our technical stack started with a monolithic Node.js app back in 2012. We have built a couple of satellite services, but we haven’t created a strategy to adopt the microservice architecture systematically. As the system becomes more complex and the team grows, we moved to a microservice architecture in early 2018. In this post, we want to share our experiences of doing it effectively and avoiding microservice syndromes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Silicon Valley</title>
      <link>https://zhangqi336.github.io/reads/2019-03-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangqi336.github.io/reads/2019-03-06/</guid>
      <description>This Is Silicon Valley (onezero.medium.com)
 Everyone wears Patagonia and North Face, everyone has AirPods hanging from their ears, and everyone goes to Lake Tahoe on weekends. And everyone talks about the same things: startups, blockchain, machine learning, and startups with blockchain and machine learning.
As Jeffrey Hammerbacher, a former Facebook executive, told Bloomberg, “The best minds of my generation are thinking about how to make people click ads.”
 The Silicon Valley author described is exactly what I see in the Silivon Valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UTC is Enough for Everyone, Right?</title>
      <link>https://zhangqi336.github.io/reads/2019-03-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangqi336.github.io/reads/2019-03-03/</guid>
      <description>UTC is Enough for Everyone, Right? (zachholman.com)
 It turns out humans have had a long, long history of poorly dealing with time, so when you hammer your head against the wall trying to deal with a timezone bug, well, you’re just the last in a long, long line of human beings that are terrible at all this! Congrats. You’re pretty unremarkable.
 The author talks about long history of time and how horrible we have been dealing with time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://zhangqi336.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangqi336.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey there, I&amp;rsquo;m Tony Xu, currently working for LinkedIn as a Software Engineer. I love technology and always follow the advancements in technology, especially in the topic of web, mobile, and AI. I have a passion for designing and creating things, notably with code. When I&amp;rsquo;m not coding, I enjoy travelling with family and make travel videos. I live in the San Francisco bay area with my fiancée Helen.
I started this blog in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friends</title>
      <link>https://zhangqi336.github.io/friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangqi336.github.io/friends/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>https://zhangqi336.github.io/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangqi336.github.io/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>